{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948080374010","data":{"timestamp":" 948080374009"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" 30bef511-aa1a-4cc9-bf34-88acd4d8162b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948080378497","data":{"timestamp":" 948080378497"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" 30bef511-aa1a-4cc9-bf34-88acd4d8162b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948080380694","data":{"timestamp":" 948080380694"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" 30bef511-aa1a-4cc9-bf34-88acd4d8162b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948080382412","data":{"timestamp":" 948080382412"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" 30bef511-aa1a-4cc9-bf34-88acd4d8162b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948080387904","data":{"timestamp":" 948080387904"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" 30bef511-aa1a-4cc9-bf34-88acd4d8162b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIANGAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948080389631","data":{"timestamp":" 948080389631"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" 30bef511-aa1a-4cc9-bf34-88acd4d8162b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948080391587","data":{"timestamp":" 948080391587"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" 30bef511-aa1a-4cc9-bf34-88acd4d8162b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948080393515","data":{"timestamp":" 948080393515"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" 30bef511-aa1a-4cc9-bf34-88acd4d8162b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948080398826","data":{"timestamp":" 948080398825"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" 30bef511-aa1a-4cc9-bf34-88acd4d8162b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUNA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948080400947","data":{"timestamp":" 948080400947"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" 30bef511-aa1a-4cc9-bf34-88acd4d8162b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948080401122","data":{"timestamp":" 948080401122"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" 30bef511-aa1a-4cc9-bf34-88acd4d8162b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948080439593","data":{"timestamp":" 948080439593"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" 30bef511-aa1a-4cc9-bf34-88acd4d8162b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948080449074","data":{"timestamp":" 948080449073"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" a8eeba59-c07a-4b71-8de5-777f3d9fec42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948080449307","data":{"timestamp":" 948080449306"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" a8eeba59-c07a-4b71-8de5-777f3d9fec42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948080450281","data":{"timestamp":" 948080450281"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" a8eeba59-c07a-4b71-8de5-777f3d9fec42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948080451570","data":{"timestamp":" 948080451570"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" a8eeba59-c07a-4b71-8de5-777f3d9fec42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948080454518","data":{"timestamp":" 948080454518"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" a8eeba59-c07a-4b71-8de5-777f3d9fec42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948080455371","data":{"timestamp":" 948080455371"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" a8eeba59-c07a-4b71-8de5-777f3d9fec42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948080455684","data":{"timestamp":" 948080455684"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" a8eeba59-c07a-4b71-8de5-777f3d9fec42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948080456928","data":{"timestamp":" 948080456928"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" a8eeba59-c07a-4b71-8de5-777f3d9fec42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948080460404","data":{"timestamp":" 948080460404"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" a8eeba59-c07a-4b71-8de5-777f3d9fec42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948080461386","data":{"timestamp":" 948080461386"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" a8eeba59-c07a-4b71-8de5-777f3d9fec42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948080461639","data":{"timestamp":" 948080461639"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" a8eeba59-c07a-4b71-8de5-777f3d9fec42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948080462581","data":{"timestamp":" 948080462581"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" a8eeba59-c07a-4b71-8de5-777f3d9fec42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948080465410","data":{"timestamp":" 948080465410"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" a8eeba59-c07a-4b71-8de5-777f3d9fec42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948080466455","data":{"timestamp":" 948080466455"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" a8eeba59-c07a-4b71-8de5-777f3d9fec42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948080466927","data":{"timestamp":" 948080466927"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" a8eeba59-c07a-4b71-8de5-777f3d9fec42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948080471419","data":{"timestamp":" 948080471419"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" a8eeba59-c07a-4b71-8de5-777f3d9fec42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948080471483","data":{"timestamp":" 948080471483"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" a8eeba59-c07a-4b71-8de5-777f3d9fec42"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948080483409","data":{"timestamp":" 948080483409"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" c36ccc35-a2b8-43af-a269-4dba51e72baf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" START_WAKATI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948080484537","data":{"timestamp":" 948080484537"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" c36ccc35-a2b8-43af-a269-4dba51e72baf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948080484609","data":{"timestamp":" 948080484609"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" c36ccc35-a2b8-43af-a269-4dba51e72baf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" START_WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948080499895","data":{"timestamp":" 948080499895"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" 91f6c8e5-5955-4b2a-94e2-b48327f9829b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_74_212-756-74"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 74"," userResponse":" 74"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948080553433","data":{"timestamp":" 948080553433"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" 91f6c8e5-5955-4b2a-94e2-b48327f9829b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_244_244-900-450"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 244"," userResponse":" 244"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948080595682","data":{"timestamp":" 948080595682"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" 91f6c8e5-5955-4b2a-94e2-b48327f9829b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_272_272-699-619"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 272"," userResponse":" 272"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948080614907","data":{"timestamp":" 948080614906"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" 91f6c8e5-5955-4b2a-94e2-b48327f9829b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_411_607-109-411"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 411"," userResponse":" 411"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948080993669","data":{"timestamp":" 948080993669"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" 91f6c8e5-5955-4b2a-94e2-b48327f9829b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_112_461-128-112"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 112"," userResponse":" 112"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081259022","data":{"timestamp":" 948081259022"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" 91f6c8e5-5955-4b2a-94e2-b48327f9829b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_414_885-512-414"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 414"," userResponse":" 414"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081281729","data":{"timestamp":" 948081281729"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" 91f6c8e5-5955-4b2a-94e2-b48327f9829b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_259_630-259-528"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 259"," userResponse":" 259"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081433907","data":{"timestamp":" 948081433907"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" 91f6c8e5-5955-4b2a-94e2-b48327f9829b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_422_420-422-684"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 422"," userResponse":" 684"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081462018","data":{"timestamp":" 948081462018"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" 91f6c8e5-5955-4b2a-94e2-b48327f9829b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_422_420-422-684"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081479232","data":{"timestamp":" 948081479232"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" db98c7ba-14f7-4c82-879e-f6932ebff171"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" START_WAKATI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081479332","data":{"timestamp":" 948081479306"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" db98c7ba-14f7-4c82-879e-f6932ebff171"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081479419","data":{"timestamp":" 948081479418"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" db98c7ba-14f7-4c82-879e-f6932ebff171"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" START_WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081488254","data":{"timestamp":" 948081488254"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" f3e168b8-94fc-442d-a981-31ba8f8c12b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081488485","data":{"timestamp":" 948081488484"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" f3e168b8-94fc-442d-a981-31ba8f8c12b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081489451","data":{"timestamp":" 948081489451"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" f3e168b8-94fc-442d-a981-31ba8f8c12b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081490733","data":{"timestamp":" 948081490733"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" f3e168b8-94fc-442d-a981-31ba8f8c12b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081493628","data":{"timestamp":" 948081493627"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" f3e168b8-94fc-442d-a981-31ba8f8c12b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081494470","data":{"timestamp":" 948081494470"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" f3e168b8-94fc-442d-a981-31ba8f8c12b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081494783","data":{"timestamp":" 948081494782"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" f3e168b8-94fc-442d-a981-31ba8f8c12b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081496016","data":{"timestamp":" 948081496016"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" f3e168b8-94fc-442d-a981-31ba8f8c12b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081499483","data":{"timestamp":" 948081499483"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" f3e168b8-94fc-442d-a981-31ba8f8c12b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081500466","data":{"timestamp":" 948081500466"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" f3e168b8-94fc-442d-a981-31ba8f8c12b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081500719","data":{"timestamp":" 948081500719"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" f3e168b8-94fc-442d-a981-31ba8f8c12b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081501670","data":{"timestamp":" 948081501670"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" f3e168b8-94fc-442d-a981-31ba8f8c12b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081504545","data":{"timestamp":" 948081504544"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" f3e168b8-94fc-442d-a981-31ba8f8c12b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081505586","data":{"timestamp":" 948081505585"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" f3e168b8-94fc-442d-a981-31ba8f8c12b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081506064","data":{"timestamp":" 948081506064"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" f3e168b8-94fc-442d-a981-31ba8f8c12b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081510650","data":{"timestamp":" 948081510649"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" f3e168b8-94fc-442d-a981-31ba8f8c12b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081510722","data":{"timestamp":" 948081510722"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" f3e168b8-94fc-442d-a981-31ba8f8c12b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081517033","data":{"timestamp":" 948081517033"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" f3e168b8-94fc-442d-a981-31ba8f8c12b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081524605","data":{"timestamp":" 948081524605"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" f3e168b8-94fc-442d-a981-31ba8f8c12b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081530707","data":{"timestamp":" 948081530706"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" f3e168b8-94fc-442d-a981-31ba8f8c12b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081539967","data":{"timestamp":" 948081539967"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" ae824669-0b21-4f90-bb49-115d78ee8ded"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081540189","data":{"timestamp":" 948081540189"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" ae824669-0b21-4f90-bb49-115d78ee8ded"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081541160","data":{"timestamp":" 948081541160"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" ae824669-0b21-4f90-bb49-115d78ee8ded"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081542434","data":{"timestamp":" 948081542434"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" ae824669-0b21-4f90-bb49-115d78ee8ded"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081545355","data":{"timestamp":" 948081545354"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" ae824669-0b21-4f90-bb49-115d78ee8ded"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081546209","data":{"timestamp":" 948081546209"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" ae824669-0b21-4f90-bb49-115d78ee8ded"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081546530","data":{"timestamp":" 948081546530"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" ae824669-0b21-4f90-bb49-115d78ee8ded"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081547777","data":{"timestamp":" 948081547777"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" ae824669-0b21-4f90-bb49-115d78ee8ded"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081551319","data":{"timestamp":" 948081551318"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" ae824669-0b21-4f90-bb49-115d78ee8ded"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081552312","data":{"timestamp":" 948081552312"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" ae824669-0b21-4f90-bb49-115d78ee8ded"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081552577","data":{"timestamp":" 948081552577"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" ae824669-0b21-4f90-bb49-115d78ee8ded"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081553532","data":{"timestamp":" 948081553532"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" ae824669-0b21-4f90-bb49-115d78ee8ded"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081556450","data":{"timestamp":" 948081556449"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" ae824669-0b21-4f90-bb49-115d78ee8ded"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081557492","data":{"timestamp":" 948081557492"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" ae824669-0b21-4f90-bb49-115d78ee8ded"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081557974","data":{"timestamp":" 948081557973"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" ae824669-0b21-4f90-bb49-115d78ee8ded"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081562548","data":{"timestamp":" 948081562547"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" ae824669-0b21-4f90-bb49-115d78ee8ded"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081562683","data":{"timestamp":" 948081562683"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" ae824669-0b21-4f90-bb49-115d78ee8ded"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081568372","data":{"timestamp":" 948081568372"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" ae824669-0b21-4f90-bb49-115d78ee8ded"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081781454","data":{"timestamp":" 948081781454"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" ae824669-0b21-4f90-bb49-115d78ee8ded"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081786086","data":{"timestamp":" 948081786086"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" ae824669-0b21-4f90-bb49-115d78ee8ded"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081795341","data":{"timestamp":" 948081795341"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" 1b930148-7056-4cd6-8e1a-91e096c1c068"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081795564","data":{"timestamp":" 948081795564"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" 1b930148-7056-4cd6-8e1a-91e096c1c068"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081796341","data":{"timestamp":" 948081796341"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" 1b930148-7056-4cd6-8e1a-91e096c1c068"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081796427","data":{"timestamp":" 948081796427"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" 1b930148-7056-4cd6-8e1a-91e096c1c068"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948081801508","data":{"timestamp":" 948081801508"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" 1b930148-7056-4cd6-8e1a-91e096c1c068"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948082075758","data":{"timestamp":" 948082075758"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" 1b930148-7056-4cd6-8e1a-91e096c1c068"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948082081325","data":{"timestamp":" 948082081324"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" 1b930148-7056-4cd6-8e1a-91e096c1c068"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948082087053","data":{"timestamp":" 948082087052"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" 1b930148-7056-4cd6-8e1a-91e096c1c068"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948082092304","data":{"timestamp":" 948082092303"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" 1b930148-7056-4cd6-8e1a-91e096c1c068"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948082099563","data":{"timestamp":" 948082099562"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" 1b930148-7056-4cd6-8e1a-91e096c1c068"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948082103763","data":{"timestamp":" 948082103762"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" 1b930148-7056-4cd6-8e1a-91e096c1c068"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948082108230","data":{"timestamp":" 948082108229"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" 1b930148-7056-4cd6-8e1a-91e096c1c068"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948082113651","data":{"timestamp":" 948082113651"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" 1b930148-7056-4cd6-8e1a-91e096c1c068"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948082179814","data":{"timestamp":" 948082179814"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" 1b930148-7056-4cd6-8e1a-91e096c1c068"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164826091","data":{"timestamp":" 948164826091"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164827778","data":{"timestamp":" 948164827777"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164832442","data":{"timestamp":" 948164832442"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" START_KIANGAZI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164836162","data":{"timestamp":" 948164836162"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164839979","data":{"timestamp":" 948164839979"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" KULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164841512","data":{"timestamp":" 948164841512"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164842310","data":{"timestamp":" 948164842310"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164844750","data":{"timestamp":" 948164844750"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIANGAZI"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164845714","data":{"timestamp":" 948164845713"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KIANGAZI"," userResponse":" START_KIANGAZI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164847801","data":{"timestamp":" 948164847801"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIANGAZI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164848679","data":{"timestamp":" 948164848678"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164848856","data":{"timestamp":" 948164848856"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164849058","data":{"timestamp":" 948164849057"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164855005","data":{"timestamp":" 948164855005"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUNA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164857353","data":{"timestamp":" 948164857353"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUNA"," userResponse":" START_WAKATI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164859186","data":{"timestamp":" 948164859185"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUNA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164860574","data":{"timestamp":" 948164860574"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" START_MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164862498","data":{"timestamp":" 948164862498"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164864446","data":{"timestamp":" 948164864445"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164868736","data":{"timestamp":" 948164868736"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164871175","data":{"timestamp":" 948164871175"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164874869","data":{"timestamp":" 948164874868"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164876985","data":{"timestamp":" 948164876984"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" HAKUNA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164878716","data":{"timestamp":" 948164878715"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164880580","data":{"timestamp":" 948164880580"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ISIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164883914","data":{"timestamp":" 948164883914"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ISIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164885847","data":{"timestamp":" 948164885845"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ISIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164888123","data":{"timestamp":" 948164888123"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" HAKUNA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164892662","data":{"timestamp":" 948164892662"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" START_KUNGURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164894264","data":{"timestamp":" 948164894263"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164895522","data":{"timestamp":" 948164895522"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164898458","data":{"timestamp":" 948164898458"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164900266","data":{"timestamp":" 948164900266"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" START_MBALI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164902558","data":{"timestamp":" 948164902558"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164904406","data":{"timestamp":" 948164904406"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164906759","data":{"timestamp":" 948164906759"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKWENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164909010","data":{"timestamp":" 948164909010"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164912604","data":{"timestamp":" 948164912604"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164915894","data":{"timestamp":" 948164915894"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164923557","data":{"timestamp":" 948164923556"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164925898","data":{"timestamp":" 948164925898"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164932161","data":{"timestamp":" 948164932160"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164934387","data":{"timestamp":" 948164934387"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATAMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164937023","data":{"timestamp":" 948164937023"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164945127","data":{"timestamp":" 948164945127"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164949370","data":{"timestamp":" 948164949370"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164951500","data":{"timestamp":" 948164951500"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164953155","data":{"timestamp":" 948164953155"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164955190","data":{"timestamp":" 948164955190"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164957279","data":{"timestamp":" 948164957279"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164959227","data":{"timestamp":" 948164959227"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIRUDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164960820","data":{"timestamp":" 948164960820"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164962716","data":{"timestamp":" 948164962716"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEBEBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164966213","data":{"timestamp":" 948164966212"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164967915","data":{"timestamp":" 948164967915"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164972553","data":{"timestamp":" 948164972552"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164974795","data":{"timestamp":" 948164974795"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWALETEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164976576","data":{"timestamp":" 948164976576"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164979416","data":{"timestamp":" 948164979416"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164984663","data":{"timestamp":" 948164984663"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOYAONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164989847","data":{"timestamp":" 948164989847"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164993654","data":{"timestamp":" 948164993654"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164994952","data":{"timestamp":" 948164994951"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164995039","data":{"timestamp":" 948164995039"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948164999862","data":{"timestamp":" 948164999862"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948165005300","data":{"timestamp":" 948165005299"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948165222697","data":{"timestamp":" 948165222695"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948165228825","data":{"timestamp":" 948165228825"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948165234946","data":{"timestamp":" 948165234946"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948165241235","data":{"timestamp":" 948165241235"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948165628493","data":{"timestamp":" 948165628493"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948165635008","data":{"timestamp":" 948165635008"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948165640113","data":{"timestamp":" 948165640112"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948165647815","data":{"timestamp":" 948165647815"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948165683545","data":{"timestamp":" 948165683545"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948165688090","data":{"timestamp":" 948165688089"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948165693491","data":{"timestamp":" 948165693491"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948165698549","data":{"timestamp":" 948165698548"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948165708581","data":{"timestamp":" 948165708580"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948165714187","data":{"timestamp":" 948165714187"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" e8db0185-fe4e-49ab-8e0a-128f32c1e23d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948165723817","data":{"timestamp":" 948165723817"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" b514a38f-5e1d-4a8f-b672-23e377f00e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948165724040","data":{"timestamp":" 948165724040"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" b514a38f-5e1d-4a8f-b672-23e377f00e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948165725009","data":{"timestamp":" 948165725009"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" b514a38f-5e1d-4a8f-b672-23e377f00e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948165726296","data":{"timestamp":" 948165726296"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" b514a38f-5e1d-4a8f-b672-23e377f00e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948165729243","data":{"timestamp":" 948165729243"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" b514a38f-5e1d-4a8f-b672-23e377f00e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948165730087","data":{"timestamp":" 948165730087"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" b514a38f-5e1d-4a8f-b672-23e377f00e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948165730400","data":{"timestamp":" 948165730400"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" b514a38f-5e1d-4a8f-b672-23e377f00e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948165731118","data":{"timestamp":" 948165731118"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" b514a38f-5e1d-4a8f-b672-23e377f00e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948165731224","data":{"timestamp":" 948165731224"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" b514a38f-5e1d-4a8f-b672-23e377f00e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948165735585","data":{"timestamp":" 948165735585"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" b514a38f-5e1d-4a8f-b672-23e377f00e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948165743621","data":{"timestamp":" 948165743621"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" b514a38f-5e1d-4a8f-b672-23e377f00e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948165752224","data":{"timestamp":" 948165752224"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" b514a38f-5e1d-4a8f-b672-23e377f00e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948165757931","data":{"timestamp":" 948165757930"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" b514a38f-5e1d-4a8f-b672-23e377f00e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948165763000","data":{"timestamp":" 948165763000"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" b514a38f-5e1d-4a8f-b672-23e377f00e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:100..800.rand.SUB-3D-H.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948165868662","data":{"timestamp":" 948165868661"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" b514a38f-5e1d-4a8f-b672-23e377f00e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948165875557","data":{"timestamp":" 948165875557"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000117_063915"," gameId":" b514a38f-5e1d-4a8f-b672-23e377f00e0a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}